<resources>
    <string name="app_name">modevt finals</string>

    <string name="how_to_play">HOW TO PLAY \n\n 1. At the start of the game, the player is given 3 tokens of life. These tokens are the lives given to you to answer the 5 questions. \n
    2. if you get a question right you will be given another token of life. If you get the answer wrong 1 life will be deducted. \n\n
    3. If you get through the 5 questions without running out of life tokens you win. If you lose all your life tokens before completing all 5 questions you lose the game.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us">ABOUT US \n \n We, students of De La Salle - College of Saint Benilde under the Information Systems program are the
key figures in developing this mobile quiz application, on which we benefit and thank the entire
Benildean community in participating in this simple quiz application in order to cherish the prosperous and
rich history of our institution and also the teachings of Saints John Baptist De La Salle and Benilde Romancon.</string>

    <string name="question_1">1. What year did De La Salle - College of Saint Benilde was founded?</string>
    <string name="Q1choiceA">A. 1975</string>
    <string name="Q1choiceB">B. 1978</string>
    <string name="Q1choiceC">C. 1980</string>
    <string name="Q1choiceD">D. 1982</string>

    <string name="question_2">2. Who is the current President of De La Salle College of Saint Benilde</string>
    <string name="Q2choiceA">A. Br. Andrew Gonzalez</string>
    <string name="Q2choiceB">B. Br. Armin Luistro</string>
    <string name="Q2choiceC">C. Br. Dennis Magbanua</string>
    <string name="Q2choiceD">D. Bro. Edmundo Fernandez</string>

    <string name="question_3">3. There are three main campuses in CSB, which is a 14 storey academic building and a big playground for creative minds that stimulates students innovative ideas and to think outside of the box.</string>
    <string name="Q3choiceA">A. Taft </string>
    <string name="Q3choiceB">B. SDA</string>
    <string name="Q3choiceC">C. AKIC</string>
    <string name="Q3choiceD">D. ATRIUM</string>

    <string name="question_4">Which of the following is not a benildean core value?</string>
    <string name="Q4choiceA">A. Perseverance and Forthright </string>
    <string name="Q4choiceB">B. professional competence</string>
    <string name="Q4choiceC">C. appreciation of individual worth</string>
    <string name="Q4choiceD">D. Sense of Nationhood</string>

    <string name="question_5">Fill in the blank in our  with the correct word among the choices below: \n\n
    "De La Salle-College of Saint Benilde, a member of De La Salle Philippines, is a Catholic, dynamic, and innovative learning community. Guided by the Lasallian principles of _ _ _ _ _, Zeal in Service and Communion in Mission, it recognizes the uniqueness of every individual and responds to the diverse needs of all learners."</string>
    <string name="Q5choiceA">A. Faith</string>
    <string name="Q5choiceB">B. Duty</string>
    <string name="Q5choiceC">C. Optimism</string>
    <string name="Q5choiceD">D. Love</string>

</resources>